[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the following line delivered by Winger when his girlfriend walks out the door after breaking up with him in the movie Stripes:\nJohn Winger: You cant go! _________________!", "correct_answer": "All the plants are gonna die!", "incorrect_answers": ["What am I gonna do with all your shoes!", "I love you!", "Wholl pay the rent?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Voyager obtain the first images of Mars?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 2005 documentary film a  large number of famous comedians show how they tell one particular dirty joke.", "correct_answer": "The Aristocrats", "incorrect_answers": ["Dirty Rotten Scoundrel", "The Elegants", "Down and Dirty Comics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Academy Awards did Martin Scorseses 2002 movie Gangs of New York win out of ten nominations?", "correct_answer": "None", "incorrect_answers": ["One", "Ten", "Two"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the Chinese Zodiac, the year of the cat occurred in 2000.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Bob from the movie What About Bob? is on the bus to go to Lake Winnipesaukee in New Hampshire, what does he have around his neck?", "correct_answer": "his goldfish Gil in a glass jar", "incorrect_answers": ["some garlic cloves in a bottle", "his lucky rabbits foot", "a container of antibacterial soap"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For his performance in what action movie did Denzel Washington win his first Academy Award for Best Actor?", "correct_answer": "Training Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Malcolm X", "Man on Fire", "Glory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Charles Darwins second son and fifth child, who became a prominent astronomer and mathematician?", "correct_answer": "George Howard Darwin", "incorrect_answers": ["Leonard Darwin", "Francis Darwin", "William Erasmus Darwin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to history/science/geology, dinosaurs became extinct approximately how many years ago?", "correct_answer": "65 million", "incorrect_answers": ["10 million", "25 million", "80 million"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following political figures was the first to fight a war as President of the United States?", "correct_answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "incorrect_answers": ["James Monroe", "Andrew Jackson", "George Washington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the smallest basic particle of matter?", "correct_answer": "Atom", "incorrect_answers": ["Mass", "Volume", "Molecule"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Will Smiths high school in Philadelphia after which his production company is named?", "correct_answer": "Overbrook", "incorrect_answers": ["McClymonds", "Clinton", "Ho-Ho-Kus"]}]